[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the Portuguese word brasa from which the name of Brazil possibly originated?", "correct_answer": "Ember", "incorrect_answers": ["Jungle", "River", "Heaven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An elephants tusks grow continuously, about 7 inches a year.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who performed the the Oscar-nominated song Blame Canada, from the movie South Park: Bigger, Longer  Uncut, at the 72nd Academy Awards ceremony in 2000?", "correct_answer": "Robin Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Vanessa Williams", "Tim Robins", "Robbie Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Reviews for the movie Eight Below were in general positive.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following fast food items provides the consumer with the greatest amount of calories from fat?", "correct_answer": "Dominos Garlic Sauce", "incorrect_answers": ["Whopper Jr. With Cheese", "Hardees 1/3 LB Mushroom and Swiss Thickburger", "Taco Bell Nachos BellGrande"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the hobby of collecting matchboxes and different match-related items called?", "correct_answer": "Phillumeny", "incorrect_answers": ["Philanthropy", "Philhellenism", "Philately"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular musician voiced Arthur in the 2007 movie Shrek the Third?", "correct_answer": "Justin Timberlake", "incorrect_answers": ["Bryan Adams", "Robbie Williams", "Jamie Foxx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term refers to the efficiency of an electric machine, measured in watt hours or kilowatt hours?", "correct_answer": "Energy Efficiency", "incorrect_answers": ["OHM", "Frequency Efficiency", "Farad"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the author of The Scarlatti Inheritance, The Matarese Cycle, The Osterman Weekend, and The Scorpio Illusion.?", "correct_answer": "Robert Ludlum", "incorrect_answers": ["John Grisham", "John Tanner", "Eric Van Lustbader"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest beat out what Steven Spielberg movie for Best Picture at the 48th annual Academy Awards?", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["E.T.: The Extra Terrestrial", "Close Encounters of the Third Kind", "Jurassic Park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which type of patient is most likely to have an AV fistula or graft?", "correct_answer": "Dialysis", "incorrect_answers": ["Arthritic", "Wheelchair-bound", "Hospice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brad Pitt starred in all these movies, except one. Can you spot it?", "correct_answer": "The Beach", "incorrect_answers": ["Meet Joe Black", "Mr.  Mrs. Smith", "Oceans Eleven"]}]